A hundred years ago,
all was right with our world.
Prosperity and peace filled our days.
The four Nations:
Water, Earth, fire and Air Nomads
lived amongst each other in harmony.
Great respect was aflorded to all those
who could bend their natural element.
The Avatar was the only person
born amongst all the nations
who could master all four elements.
He was the only one who could
communicate with the Spirit World.
With the Spirits' guidance,
the Avatar kept balance in the world.
And then, a hundred years ago,
he just disappeared.
Re-Sync by tebawihi
l'm sorry. l'm sorry!
Hey, l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, l'm sorry, l'm sorry!
l'm sorry! l'm sorry! Hey!
It worked better that time.
l thought about Mom. Isn't that strange?
Yeah. l guess so.
Just stop doing that stuff around me.
l always get wet.
My brother and l live
in the Southern Water Tribe,
which was once a big city.
Our father is off fighting in The War.
My mother was taken prisoner
and killed when l was young.
ln this time of war, food is scarce.
My brother and l often
go hunting for food,
but, unfortunately, my brother
isn"t the best hunter in the world.
- Tiger seal.
- Are you sure?
l did everything Dad said to do.
l watched which side of the fin tracks
are more indented.
That shows which
direction they're going.
l saw how long the drag skids are.
That shows you how fast they're going.
There's something under there.
lt's a cave-in!
Move away from the cracks!
Katara, don't go near it.
This is probably some Fire Nation trick.
Just back away really slow.
Katara! Do not hit that sphere!
Uncle, look!
ls he breathing?
Did you see that light
shoot into the sky?
What's your name?
How did you get here?
How did you get in the ice?
He's exhausted.
We need to get him back to the village.
What is this thing?
lt's trying to eat me!
Look. See?
How'd you get all the way out here?
l ran away from home.
We got in a storm. We were forced
under the water of the ocean.
l see.
lt wasn't very smart. l was just upset.
- Thanks for saving me.
- Lucky.
l probably should get home.
They'll all be worried.
- You're not still upset?
- Not as much as l was.
The Fire Nation is here.
- What?
- And they brought their machines.
Don't come out
till l tell you it's safe.
- Is something wrong?
- No. Please wait here.
- Hurry, now!
- Secure the area!
lt can't be coincidence
that we break him out of the ice,
light shoots into the sky and now the
Fire Nation is here with their machines.
Sokka, don't.
l am Prince Zuko...
...son of Fire Lord Ozai
and heir to the throne!
Bring me all your elderly!
- Papa!
- Move!
Yeah?
Grandma!
Please don't... don't harm him!
Come on!
Katara, don't.
- Form a line!
- Come on!
Here.
Hey.
Grammy!
You're scaring these people.
Who are you? What's your name?!
- l don't need to tell you anything.
- Firebenders!
l'm taking you to my ship.
lf you don't come,
l'll burn down this village.
l'll go with you.
Don't hurt anyone.
They were looking for someone old
and they were looking for someone
with the same markings the boy had.
They dragged Mom away
the same way when we were babies.
She wouldn't have watched us being
taken away. She would have fought.
We found that boy. He's our
responsibility. We should fight.
What would you do
if they tried to take me away?
l'd kill them all.
- Why?
- Because you're my sister.
Because Dad told me
to protect you with my life.
Because l'm your responsibility.
And this boy is our responsibility.
What do you want us to do, Katara?
How are we supposed to save him?
They're on a ship.
We'd need a miracle to catch them.
l know you think everything's
going to work out, but l don't.
His bison creature thing floats.
What do you want with me?
My nephew wants me to perform
a little test on you.
- What kind of test?
- l assure you, it won't hurt.
l've performed it hundreds of times.
It only takes a few moments.
And then you're free to go.
Would you mind if l put a few things
in front of you at the table?
lt will only take a moment.
That's all you want?
My name is Iroh,
and you have my word.
Grandma, l know
you're gonna try to stop us,
- but this is iust something l need...
- Sit down.
l knew from the first time
we discovered you were a Bender,
that one day,
l would realize your destiny.
There hasn't been a Waterbender
in the Southern Water Tribe
since my friend Hama was taken away.
Today, l found out that destiny.
Did you see that boy's tattoos?
Tattoos like that haven't
been seen in over a century.
l believe they are Airbending tattoos.
How can that be?
l believe that little boy
might be the Avatar.
Once, a long time ago,
the Spirit World kept balance over us.
What is the Spirit World, Grandma?
lt's not a place made up
of things you can touch.
But it exists, nonetheless.
lt is filled with the most amazing forms
of dazzling creatures...
...that exist in the most
exotic valleys, mountains and forests.
Each of these creatures is a Spirit.
They've watched over us
since the beginning.
They have guided us. And only
the Avatar can go speak to them.
Aren't there Spirits here?
Yes, there are some Spirits
that live hidden among us,
sure they're watching us
with great sadness...
The Fire Nation doesn't wish
to live by the Spirits.
That's why they're so frightened
by the existence of the Avatar.
- What can he do?
- With his mastery of the four elements,
he will begin to change hearts.
And it is in the heart
that all wars are won.
Now, go help this boy.
He will need you two.
And we all need him.
You are my prisoner...
...Airbender.
l'm taking you back to the Fire Nation.
- You said...
- l apologize.
l should have explained further.
lf you failed the test, as all others
did, you were free to leave.
But, as it turns out, you are
the only one in the entire world
who could pass this test.
lt is truly an honor
to be in your presence.
Don't even try to escape.
This is a warship!
Stop! There's no way you can...
Don't move! You have nowhere to run!
Halt!
Don't let him escape!
Get him!
Thanks for bringing Appa to me.
The Fire Nation is up to something.
l have to go back now.
- We'll come with you.
- l can take you back to the village.
We're going with you.
You found the Avatar.
For a moment, l had my honor back.
Your destinies are tied, Zuko.
That, you can be sure of.
Aang flew us to his home. He told us
how he leff there in a storm on Appa,
and got forced into the ocean
where they almost drowned.
Aang Airbended a sphere around them,
and ice formed.
And he couldn"t remember
anything after that.
Hey, Chinto! Monae! l'm back!
Hey, guys! l want you to meet someone!
This is where you live?
They must be playing some trick
or something.
Monk Gyatso is gonna try and iump out
and scare me at any moment.
He's the teacher responsible for me.
He's kind of like my father.
- Is it OK if you tell me your name?
- The monks named me Aang.
OK, guys! Enough!
Spider-rat!
They're poisonous! Get behind me.
He's a flying lemur-bat.
We keep them as pets.
Weren't they extinct a long time ago?
Extinct? No, there must be thousands
of them on this mountain.
Your friends were monks?
l know where they are right now.
They're at the prayer field!
Aang, wait! l have to talk to you!
Aang...
...l think you were in that ice
for almost a hundred years.
- The Firebenders started a war.
- l left a few days ago.
Aang, the Fire Nation knew the Avatar
would be born into the Air Nomads...
...so they exterminated
all the Air Nomads.
You're lying!
This is Monk Gyatso's.
l made it for him.
No!
Katara! Stay away from him!
Katara!
Stay away from him!
Your friends were monks?
The Avatar?
Where have you been?
Aang!
You can"t bring Monk Gyatso back,
but Sokka and l can be with you
as long as you need!
Don"t give up! We can do this together!
Aang!
The banished prince.
Let's offer him lunch.
l wanted to thank
the great General Iroh
and young Prince Zuko
for dining with us.
As you know, the Fire Lord
has banished his son, the Prince,
and renounced his love of him, and will
not let him return to the throne
unless he finds the Avatar.
The Fire Lord believes his son
is too soft
and by doing this,
he will become strong
and become a worthy heir
to the throne.
l commend the Fire Lord's discipline.
For example, it seems
l need to remind Prince Zuko
that, during his banishment,
he is an enemy of the Fire Nation
and is not allowed
to wear the Fire Nation uniform.
But we will let him wear it today,
like a child wearing a costume.
One day, my father will take me back
and you will bow before me.
You OK?
l'll be fine.
You know, my grandma thinks
because you're an Airbender,
that you could be the Avatar.
How much does
the Fire Nation control?
A lot of villages in the Earth Kingdom,
like around here.
They haven't been able to conquer
big cities, like Ba Sing Se,
but they're making plans, l'm sure.
So...
...are you the Avatar, Aang?
What is this?
Stay hidden.
- That child is being arrested.
- For what?
He was bending tiny stones at us
from behind a tree. It really hurt.
He can bend earth?
Earthbending is forbidden
in this village.
Leave him alone.
You're not taking him anywhere.
No one is taking anybody away!
She's a bender!
Katara!
Move.
You, too.
Dad!
- This is my father.
- Hello.
That's the Fire Nation's plan,
suppress all other bending.
How did this happen to your village?
Fire Nation sent soldiers.
We fought them and defeated them.
Then they sent their machines,
huge machines made of metal.
There was nothing we could do.
Those who could not bend were
allowed to live in peace,
if we were imprisoned.
Earthbenders!
Why are you acting this way?
You are powerful and amazing people!
You don't need to live like this!
There is earth right beneath your feet.
The ground is an extension
of who you are!
lf the Avatar had returned...
...would that mean anything to you?
The Avatar is dead.
If he was here, he would protect us.
My name is Aang...
...and l am the Avatar.
l ran away, but l'm back now.
lt's time for you to stop doing this!
The Avatar would have to be an
Airbender. Are you an Airbender, boy?
Leave him alone!
How is he doing that?
l don't want to hurt anyone.
All Airbenders should be dead.
Kill him! Firebenders, positions!
OK! Everybody can help us now!
Don't be afraid!
Just leave them!
Fall back!
Go! He's an Airbender!
They took away any tools
related to bending.
The Fire Nation took this scroll
from a member of your Water Tribe.
A Waterbending scroll.
This is rare.
My mom told me about these.
This was you when
you were born an Earthbender,
two lifetimes ago.
You came to our village.
Avatar Kyoshi loved games.
l do, too.
l mean, l still do.
A lot of the villages in this part
of the Earth Kingdom are occupied
by the Fire Nation,
like this village was.
They prey on the weakest towns
and villages.
We should go visit
some of these towns, Aang.
- l need to tell you something.
- What is it, Aang?
l ran away before they trained me
to be the Avatar.
l don't know how
to bend the other elements.
Why did you run away?
The day they told me l was the Avatar,
they said l could never
have a normal life,
that l could never have a family.
They said it cannot work with
the responsibilities of the Avatar.
- Why can't the Avatar have a family?
- l asked that!
They said that's the sacrifice
the Avatar always has to make.
OK. So, what if we found you teachers.
Teachers to teach you bending?
Which element would you
have to learn first?
Water. Water comes
after Air in the cycle.
Air, Water, Earth, Fire.
But there are really powerful benders
in the Northern Water Tribe.
My dad told me about it before he left.
lt's led by a princess because
her father died.
There are teachers there, but all
the way on the other side of the world.
- We can get there on Appa.
- That's what l was thinking.
And maybe we can stop
in the villages on the way,
start a change in The War
in these small villages.
- Should we try it?
- Yes, we should.
The scroll we had
was proving to be helpful.
Aang was practicing,
but for some reason,
he was having trouble
with Waterbending.
We moved from town to town
in the Earth Kingdom.
We tried to stay out of sight,
but Sokka became concerned
we were being followed.
Sire, l have good news.
As you know, l conducted a raid
on the Great Library,
- which most said didn't exist.
- Get on with it.
l found scrolls in the library.
We are deciphering them.
But l believe they may
contain information
as to where the Ocean and Moon
Spirits live in this world.
With this information,
we could bring down
the Northern Water Tribe city,
we could show the world
the true strength of fire.
l am pleased.
Well, Commander Zhao,
are the rumors true or not?
Our spies have discovered someone
claiming to be the Avatar.
They describe him as just a boy.
We should set a trap for this person.
We have many Earth Kingdom people
under our control.
l can leave soldiers
hidden in certain locations.
- And my son?
- He had his chance. He missed it.
Let's hope, for your sake,
my son doesn't find this person first
and he turns out to be the Avatar.
He would return as a hero and,
for all purposes, be your superior.
Well, l suppose it's a race, then.
We're close, Uncle.
They've been moving
farther and farther north.
We're catching them.
There are a lot of pretty girls
in this town, Zuko.
You could fall in love here.
We could settle down here,
and you could have a blessed life.
We don't have to continue this, Zuko.
l'll show you why we must, Uncle.
Hey. Hey. Little one, come here.
You look like a very smart boy.
Tell me what you know about the
Prince, the Fire Lord's son.
- He did something wrong.
- He spoke out of turn to a general,
in defense of some of his friends
who were going to be sacrificed
in a battle.
Then Prince Zuko
was sentenced to an Agni Kai duel,
but when he showed up,
- it was his father he was to fight.
- That's right.
He would not fight his father.
Then his father mocked him and said,
''l should bring your sister
up here to beat you.''
Then the father burnt his son...
...to teach him a lesson.
We'll catch him soon, Uncle.
Then we can think
about the pretty girls.
Aang...
Try to keep your wrist bent,
like it's showing.
What's wrong?
You've really been distracted today.
l saw Sokka's maps.
We're near the Northern Air Temple.
Do you think it would be OK
if l just visited there and came back?
- l'd be back in less than a day.
- Why?
He had a vision
at the Southern Air Temple prayer field.
He talked to a Dragon Spirit
who he thinks can help us.
He thinks if he goes
to another spiritual place,
he can get back to the Spirit World.
l don't think that's a good idea.
We started a rebellion.
Try to talk him out of it.
l can't do this.
l need help.
- l guess your talk didn't work.
- He'll be back in a day.
The Fire Nation is following us. If we
make a wrong move, they'll catch him.
Who are you?
Why, it cannot be!
l've heard stories. Are you...?
My name is Aang.
l cannot believe
l've lived to see your return.
l'm an Earth villager,
but l visit these temple remains often.
The Fire Nation destroyed this temple.
They have ruined everything.
No, no, no, not everything.
You know, there's
a hidden chamber of statues
l think you, of all people, should see.
These are all the Avatars.
These are the reincarnations
of you over the years.
The Avatar Roku was your last life.
Now, how did the Airbenders know
you were the Avatar, little one?
They gave me a test.
They put 1,000 toys in front of me
and asked me to choose four.
They said l chose the same four obiects
that belonged to the previous Avatars.
That's when they told me
l could have no family.
Told me l had a responsibility
to the Four Nations.
There's a ceremony
when everyone bows to me.
That's when l accept my role
as the Avatar.
But when everyone bowed...
...l didn't bow back.
You seem like a nice young man.
You really do.
You will forgive me, won't you?
- For what?
- For luring you down here.
l have lived in poverty
because of your absence, Avatar.
So you will understand
my actions today.
l have lived in poverty
because of your absence, Avatar.
l have seen a vision
of the moon turning red.
The Fire Nation has stolen knowledge
of us from the Great Library.
They are planning
to misuse this knowledge.
l will stop them.
You must go
to the Northern Water Tribe.
lf they take that city,
more will suffer and die,
as your Airbenders have.
You must go now!
Will l stop them?
Wake up, young man!
My name is Commander Zhao.
l set this trap for you.
Don't worry, l'm not gonna kill you.
Besides, you'd just be reborn again,
and then the search would continue.
So where have you been all this time?
And how is it that you're still a boy?
l understand that when you freed
that handful of towns,
you were very impressive, but...
...you only used Airbending
against my soldiers.
Now, why is that?
The Fire Lord and l have a plan
to ensure our reign
and the downfall of our enemies.
l am sending a personal message
to the Fire Lord,
informing him
that the once feared Avatar
is our prisoner
and no threat to our might.
Who are you?
Wait! Don't!
Stop!
Fools.
Close the inner gates!
The Avatar has escaped!
Lock down the gate!
Lock down all the gates!
To the main post!
This was their practice area.
Go again!
Do not kill the Avatar!
He will just be reborn again!
Why are you doing this? Who are you?
Open the gates.
Let them out!
- Is it some kind of Spirit, Commander?
- Not at all.
Do it.
What is this?
And how did he escape?
l fear that your son
is not only incompetent,
but also a traitor.
Of course, l cannot prove this, sire.
You think...
...my son is this person
the soldiers are calling
the Blue Spirit.
Yes.
Zhao's men were searching the coast,
Iooking for you.
They also searched the ship.
l told them you went
on vacation with a girl.
Where were you the past four days?
Nowhere.
We have to keep moving.
The Avatar is traveling again.
Take rest first.
lt looks like you
went through a great deal.
When you wake, we'll have tea together
before we start the engines.
Do not harm my son.
Leave him to his isolation.
You have my word, sire.
l will not harm him.
Zuko!
And what of the Avatar ?
We assume he has
rejoined with his supporters.
lt has been confirmed
that he's traveling north.
lt is my strong belief that he is
traveling to the Northern Water Tribe.
l believe the child Avatar has only
knowledge of his birth element, Air.
l believe he is tying to learn
in the discipline of water.
He's gone to seek out someone
in the Northern Water Tribe,
where they have lived beyond our reach
and openly practice Waterbending.
We arrived at the Northern Water Tribe.
We presented ourselves
to the royal court.
My brother and the princess
became friends right away.
Aang showed them he
was the last Airbender,
and was accepted
to train with the master.
The city knew our arrival
would bring great danger.
And they prepared for war they knew
would come in the ensuing weeks.
The city was designed
to withstand any assault.
lf we keep them to the courtyard
and the marketplace till night falls,
where we have the advantage,
we will succeed.
lf we let too many of them
into the city,
their sheer numbers
could overwhelm us.
As many fires in this city should be put
out as possible when the alarm sounds.
We want to minimize
their bender sources.
l must assign a guard
to be with you at all times, Princess.
Your presence is our inspiration.
l'll do it. That's me.
l'll be her guard.
Nothing will happen to her.
l had a feeling you might volunteer.
l've heard no word of my son
for quite some time.
- Do you know where he is?
- l've not heard of anything, sire.
l'm sure word of him
will come to us soon.
The Northern Water Tribe benders
are given their strength
by the Moon and Ocean Spirits.
They will be difficult to defeat.
Now, if for some reason
the Spirits were not involved,
that would be different.
What have you learned
from the stolen scrolls?
We have deciphered the location
of the Moon and Ocean Spirits.
lt is our destiny to have found
this information, Zhao.
Eliminate the Spirits,
take the city and we will have
thwarted the Avatar in the process.
Water is what?
The flowing element.
The element of change.
To master water,
you must release your emotions,
wherever they may lead you.
Water teaches us acceptance.
Let your emotions flow like water.
Aang, would you like to spar?
You haven't sparred in a few days.
Now, use offense, Aang!
General Iroh, l'm glad you could
accept my invitation to join us
- on this historic event.
- Your invitation was most gracious.
You are a gifted strategist.
No one can argue that.
Your failure in the Hundred Day Siege
of Ba Sing Se won't be held against you.
Your son died in that siege, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
Again, l offer my condolences
on your nephew burning to death
in that terrible accident.
Thank you.
l've loved spending
these weeks with you, Sokka.
Me, too.
Should we see what the ocean
is doing today?
When there is some safety for all of us,
l will come visit our sister city
in the Southern Water Tribe
and spend some time in your home.
That would be great.
But l warn you...
...my grandmother will ask you
a lot of questions.
What might she ask me?
She'll say, ''Why is your hair white,
young lady? You look very odd.''
l would say to your grandmother, my
hair is white because when l was born
l was not awake.
My mother and father could not get me
to make a sound or move.
So they prayed for days
to the Moon Spirit
and dipped me into the sacred waters.
My parents said that my hair turned
white then and life poured into me.
Wow.
You didn't tell me that.
You didn't ask me.
Only your grandmother did.
l'm sure Zhao was the one
who ordered the attack on you.
Any problems?
We have arrived at the Northern
Water Tribe's stronghold.
They believe the boy is there.
Why do you seem upset, Uncle?
Zhao has no sacredness.
Are you sure you want to be here?
l will not be allowed to live in peace
until l bring the Avatar to my father!
ls that not clear to you?
What is this?
Yue...
...the Fire Nation is here.
Now be sure to keep your uniform
closed up to your neck.
And remember, your Chi can warm you.
l know, Uncle.
Be safe.
Aang needs to ask you something.
l have to talk to the Dragon Spirit.
He can help me defeat the Fire Nation.
ls there a spiritual place
where l can meditate?
There is a very spiritual place.
The city was built around this place.
But we must hury.
Momo, be nice.
To get your Airbending tattoos,
you have to meditate for long
periods of time without losing focus.
Some of the great monks
can meditate for four days.
- l have to get back.
- l'll take you.
l'll stay with him.
Aang?
Aang, can you hear me?
l knew you were real.
l always knew you'd return.
Me, too.
The Fire Lord's son.
You took him from our village.
Who are you?
My name is Katara,
and l'm the only Waterbender left
in the Southern Water Tribe.
- Go for the children.
- Yes.
l'm not allowed to go home without him.
The Waterbenders get power
from the moon.
They will get stronger
as the day comes to an end.
General Iroh,
l've been keeping a secret.
And what is that?
ln my raid of the Great Library
earlier this year,
l found a scroll that tells
the location
of the Ocean and Moon Spirits.
To meet a Spirit would be a great honor.
Well, l hope l can give you that honor.
What happened?
Prince Zuko's here in the city.
He took Aang again.
We'll iust wait
till everyone's fighting everyone.
Then in the night, we'll slip out.
Aang, can you hear me?
l knew you were real.
l always knew you'd return.
Hello! Hello!
Please, tell me how
to beat the Fire Nation!
You are not dealing
with the loss of your people,
and your responsibility
for their deaths.
You are stopping yourself
from grieving.
You are angry.
You must let this go.
As the Avatar,
you are not meant to hurt others.
Use the ocean.
Show them the power of Water.
Go! Do this now.
My sister Azula
was always the special one.
She was a Firebending prodigy.
My father loves her.
He can't even look at me sometimes.
He says l'm like my mother.
l advise that you
pull back your men soon.
They will be trapped in the city
when the moon's power comes out.
Do not worry about the moon's power,
General Iroh.
Why should you not be worried
about the moon's power?
Because your brother,
Fire Lord Ozai, and l
have decided it is in our best
interests to kill the Moon Spirit.
What?
Calm down. We'll find him.
Are you OK?
Did the Spirits tell you anything?
Yes. The Dragon Spirit talked to me.
l know what to do.
Aang, we have to go.
You won't be killed by Waterbenders
if you stay hidden here.
We could be friends, you know.
They're getting stronger.
This is a scroll from the Great Library.
This is our map.
Our world is going to change soon,
gentlemen.
Right there and right there.
See where they're going!
l'll go join the fight!
They are called many names:
Yin and Yang, push and pull.
May l introduce you to the mysterious
Ocean and Moon Spirits?
Why do Spirits take the form
of such benign things?
lt leaves them so vulnerable.
To teach man kindness and humility.
Commander Zhao,
there are certain things
humankind should not tamper with.
The Spirits and the Spirit World
is one of them.
What are you doing here?
Stop, Zhao.
The world will go out of balance.
Everyone will be hurt.
The Fire Nation is too powerful
to worry about children's superstitions,
General Iroh.
Commander Zhao, don't.
We are now the gods!
No!
Man all battle stations!
You are too soft, General Iroh.
He's making fire out of nothing!
They're breaching the wall!
To the front!
As the Avatar,
you are not meant to hurt others.
You must show them
the power of Water.
All is lost.
You have been anointed
by the Moon Spirit.
- He gave me life when l was a child.
- Then there is still a chance.
You can give your life
back for the Spirit's.
- Don't listen to him, he's Fire Nation.
- Nothing is ever truly lost.
- Is it mine to give back, if l choose?
- There are reasons each of us are born.
We have to find those reasons.
- This was the reason l was born.
- Yue, please.
There is no love without sacrifice.
Yue, what are you doing?
You don't know what will happen.
l believe my life force will leave my
body and return to the Moon Spirit.
And then what?
My soul will no longer exist
in this form.
Please don't do this.
There must be another way.
l can't let you do this.
l'm supposed to protect you.
My people are dying, Sokka.
Those who are in charge of others
have a responsibility.
lt is time we show the Fire Nation
we believe in our beliefs
- as much as they believe in theirs.
- But Yue...
l'm scared.
Don't make me any more scared.
l will miss you more than you know.
l killed you.
Come away from him, nephew.
There are too many soldiers now.
They will never
Iet you take the Avatar.
We must leave immediately.
He wants to fight you
so he can capture you, Zuko.
Walk away!
Come!
You stand alone.
And that has always
been your great mistake.
Water teaches us acceptance.
Let your emotions flow like water.
Aang?
They want you to be their Avatar, Aang.
We all do.
Our forces in the Northern Water Tribe
have failed to take the city.
General Zhao was killed in battle
and my brother has become a traitor.
My son's proven himself a failure.
Now, Sozin's Comet
is returning in three years.
lt will give all Firebenders the ability
of the highest Firebenders,
the ability to use their own Chi
to create Fire.
That is the day we will win this war
and prove the Fire Nation's dominance.
Now you must stop the Avatar
from mastering Earth and Fire.
You must give us the time
to get to that day.
Do you accept this
unspeakably important task
l'm putting in your hands?
l do, Father.
Re-Sync by tebawihi